crowdstorm.co.uk 2008-12-18

# Expert Product Reviews | Crowdstorm UK

## Privacy Policy

The following privacy policy sets out the privacy practices of Crowdstorm Limited relating to its web site www.smoop.com which is registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 - further information at www.ico.gov.uk

We take users' privacy very seriously. This policy sets out what is done with the personal data (information about you) which you send to us.

We reserve the right to supply your personal data in response to a request by lawyers or the courts including without limitation your computer IP address and otherwise to defend ourselves.

We do not pass your personal data to anyone or market to you without your consent. **We will never sell your data to anyone.** If at any time you wish us to remove any personal data you have posted on a posting/comment on the Site notify us and we will remove it within 30 days. We ask you to provide your real name and display that information in your user profile and so you agree to our processing and displaying that personal data of yours in that way.

We may access your account to engage in servicing and solve technical issues. Where we use a third party contractor to help run or manage the site they too may have access to your personal data but always subject to conditions of confidentiality.

### Your information

By supplying to us information to go on the site (such as you Comments on products) you consent to it being used in that way.

Apart from any material you choose to include in a Comment the rest of the information you send to us is private such as your name and address and email address. We use this to deal with your use of the Site and otherwise as set out in this Privacy Policy and as state on the Site. Your information may also be stored in any back up or other automatic caching or other service we use for our IT systems in general which may be held by a third party acting for us. We may use your email address to contact you about any issue relating to the Site. This private information is only used to run your account and would only be disclosed where required by law, where demanded by legal advisers or to protect other members of the Site. You should update your information from time to time as it alters so we always have the current details.

Other information is for the public part of the site such as your age, height, gender, photograph. It is clear on the Site which information is intended to be published on the Site and you consent to this publication. Public information is accessible all over the world wherever there is internet access and could be exported and you consent to this by using the Site. Under the Data Protection Act 1998 export of data from the EEA is permitted if you consent even to countries without the same standards of data protection as the EEA.

We also gather information such as your type of browser and IP address which we may gather for all users of the site.

If we were to sell the assets of our business we reserve the right to pass all personal data we hold to the buyers of those assets subject to confidentiality undertakings and provided they comply with our then privacy policy in relation to our data.

This policy applies to our Site. If you move to a different Site via a link or you email anyone through use of the Site then you will need to establish with them how they will use your personal data before proceeding.

### Cookies

Our site uses Cookies. The [Information Advertising Bureau](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) provide in depth information about cookies. This site also tells you [how to remove cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/) from your browser.

### Changes to the Policy

We may change our privacy policy from time to time and will make this clear on our Site if it is done.

### Email marketing

If you do not want to be marketed to us by email then you can contact us to stop that at any time. It will take us about 30 days to change our records. We will always ensure all marketing is in accordance with the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 and the Data Protection Act 1998 and other legislation from time to time in force. We do not currently market to customers by telephone or post or fax.

### Contact

Contact us for queries about our privacy policy or to notify us to cease holding your personal data at.

Crowdstorm Limited, registered office is at 67-69 George Street, London W1U 8LT, a company incorporated in England Company No. 05770816, email info@crowdstorm.com.
